(Sheldon:)And I certainly don't need someone
telling on me to my mother.
Wait, where are you going?
To my room and no one's allowed in.
[DOOR SLAMS]
- He gets his temper from his daddy.
- Ah.
- He's got my eyes.
- I see.
(Mrs Cooper:)All that science stuff,
that comes from Jesus.
Sheldon, your mom made dinner.
SHELDON:
I'm not hungry.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh. Leonard, don't trouble yourself.
He's stubborn.
He may stay in there till the rapture.
(Penny:)Are we so sure that's a bad thing?
(Mrs Cooper:)I love the boy to death...
(Mrs Cooper:)...but he has been difficult
since he fell out of me at the Kmart.
(Howard:)Excuse me for being so bold...
(Howard:)...but I now see where Sheldon gets
his smoldering good looks.
Oh. Honey, that ain't gonna work,
but you keep trying.
(Mrs Cooper:)I made chicken.
(Mrs Cooper:)I hope that isn't one of the animals
that you people think is magic.